JINHONG "JIN" CHOI

■ 617-803-3057 | ■ jinhong.choi@gmail.com | 🛅 jinhongchoi-osu | 🗘 imreburn

SUMMARY

Experienced in multiple projects for cyber-physical systems (CPS), with a focus on drones, during my MS in Computer Science. Possesses a strong foundation in both computer science and mechanical engineering, backed by 3 years of work experience in the automotive industry. Driven by a vision to develop advanced middlewares for various CPS, from IoT devices to ground and air vehicles, that meets the evolving demands of both the present and the future.

EDUCATION

Oregon State University Corvallis, OR

Master of Science in Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (GPA: 3.83/4.00) Apr 2019 – Aug 2024

Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT)

Completed 72 credits towards graduate degree in Mechanical Engineering (GPA: 4.8/5.0) Sep 2010 – Jan 2014

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Bachelors of Science in Mechanical Engineering, Minor in Business Management Mar 2003 – Jan 2010

Graduated summa cum laude (GPA: 3.91/4.00)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Oregon State University Corvallis, OR

Graduate Research/Teaching Assistant
Conducted three projects with FAA regarding cyber-physical security and safety of Unmanned Aircraft System (UAS)

Conducted a project with OMIC to enhance human-robot teaming via improvements to nonverbal robot expression

• Lectured labs and recitations, held office hours, and graded assignments for Operating Systems II, Algorithms and

Data Structures courses

Hyundai KEFICO

Gunpo, South Korea Feb 2016 – Feb 2019

Cambridge, MA

Daejeon, South Korea

 Prototyped gasoline fuel injectors under development, specialized to control femto-second laser machines for precise drilling of fuel spray holes

LX Hausys (previously LG Hausys)

Researcher in Prototype Development Team

Seoul, South Korea Feb 2010 – Jun 2010

Seoul, South Korea

Consulted on optically transparent adhesive used in touchscreens for mobile devices

Hantouch

Researcher (alternative to mandatory military service)

Feb 2007 - May 2009

• Developed resistive touchscreens integrated with mobile devices, securing three patents in South Korea

PROJECTS

Consultant

Crazyflie | C, Python

Jun 2023 - Present

- Implemented theoretical algorithms for indoor, palm-sized drones
- · Conducted experiments with a swarm of drones, enabling wireless communication and decentralized operation
- · Built an indoor testbed for drones, including a positioning system

TECHNICAL SKILLS & LANGUAGES

Programming Languages C/C++, Python, Julia, Haskell, MATLAB, LaTeX

Platforms FreeRTOS, ROS, Linux, Protobuf, CAN/LIN

Tools Git, VS Code, AutoCAD

Languagues Korean (Native), English (Professional)

PUBLICATIONS

- [1] Unmesh Uttam Patil, **Jinhong Choi**, and Houssam Abbas. "OUT-HERD: Opportunistic UAV Takeover for Herding Malfunctioning Drones". In: 2024 IEEE 27th International Conference on Intelligent Transportation Systems (ITSC). 2024.
- [2] Jinhong Choi and Yeongjin Jang. "A Survey on Sensor False Data Injection Attacks and Countermeasures in Cyber-Physical and Embedded Systems". In: Information Security Applications: 23rd International Conference, WISA 2022, Revised Selected Papers. Springer. 2022.